Guide to the Gary Stevenson Papers WAG.182
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory
  - Uruguay, 1954 - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Uruguay, 1961 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Utchitel, J. (Israel) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Utica, New York, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Van Cortlandt Park Campaign, 1962 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Venezuela, 1948 - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Vladeck Memorial, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Wajn, Hersz and Family, 1962 - 1963 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Waksman, Joseph, 1961 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Walicki, Iser, 1957 - 1963 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Warehouse, 1958 - 1962 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Warehouse, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Warehouse, 1965 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Warsaw Ghetto Memorial, 1964 - 1968 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Waserman, Herszko, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Washington, D.C., 1958 - 1963 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Waterbury, Connecticut, 1957 - 1962 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - W.E.V.D., 1964 - 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Windsor, Canada, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Winnipeg, Canada, 1960 - 1966 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Winograd, Israel (Australia), 1961 - 1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Women's Aid Society for Lithuanian Jews, Inc., 1959 - 1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Women's Division, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Worcester, Massachusetts, 1962 - 1964 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Workmen's Circle, 1956 - 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Workmen's Circle Branches (Newcomers), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Workmen's Circle Division, 1963 - 1965 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Workmen's Circle Division, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - World Jewish Congress, 1963 - 1965 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - World Refugee Year, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Yiddish Dictionary, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Yivo Institute for Jewish Research, 1957 - 1963 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Youngtown, Arizona, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Youngstown, Ohio, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Yugoslavia, 1958 - 1961 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Zborowsky, Elia, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Zippin, Julius, 1963 - 1966 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Election Results, Flyers, TDU Publications, Autozone v. Local 28, and IBT Memos (Box 21)
  - Oversized and Fragile Materials, Including Drawings, Buttons, a Poster, Cassette Tapes, a 3.5" Floppy Disk, and Bumper Stickers (Box 22)